longrangehunting.com 2017-05-29

# Long Range Hunting, LLC Privacy Policy

Long Range Hunting PRIVACY POLICY

Long Range Hunting, LLC, ("LRH") is the operator of the LongRangeHunting website: www.LongRangeHunting.com, and a variety of related websites and activities. As part of its business, LRH gathers personally identifiable information on its websites as well as anonymous data regarding the website and your activities on the site. LRH takes its privacy obligations very seriously.

This policy outlines the treatment of information LRH collects online.

Collection of Personally Identifiable Information:  
Whenever LRH collects personally identifiable about you it reserves the right to use that information for marketing the LRH and its various activities. LRH shall use the personally identifiable data collected to undertake a variety of marketing activities including, but not limited to, email, direct mail, site personalization, telephone marketing and other digital and traditional methods of advertising and communication. LRH does not sell or "monetize" data to 3rd parties. LRH, however, does and will send marketing messages on behalf of its sponsors. It will do so without giving any of your personally identifiable information to those sponsors and partners for their own use. Users can opt-out easily by clicking on an UNSUBSCRIBE link found in each such email message.

LRH does use cookies on its site to learn about the activities of its site users. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Each web site can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a web site to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. (Each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences.) If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use LRH products or services that require you to "sign in," and you may not be able to take full advantage of all offerings. However, many LRH products and services do not require that you accept cookies.

In addition, we allow certain of our Sponsors and marketing partners to set and access their cookies on your computer. Those companies provide auditing, research and reporting for marketing and advertising purposes. Advertisers' and researchers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the LRH Privacy Policy.

Collection of Non-Personally Identifiable Information:  
LRH's site technology has the ability to collect data other than personally identifiable information. LRH may collect information about your computer configuration, such as your browser type, operating system, or ISP domain name. LRH may collect information about the site you last visited prior to LRH or about your activity during your visit to the LRH site. This information will not reveal your personal identity (it is anonymous), may be used by LRH to administer the technical and operational aspects of this site, and may include identifying and using your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server. Your IP address may also be used to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

Material Changes to Policy:  
LRH may make material changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time. Therefore, you should periodically visit this page to view the current Privacy Policy. In the event of a material change to this Privacy Policy, LRH shall send an email advising of the change to all whose email addresses we have collected and retained pursuant to the terms set forth above.
